http://www.opentechsupport.net/privacy.htm

IT Security for your Business
What is Business Technology Management?
Business Technology Solutions
Business Strategies
Developing Business IT Strategies
How to Run a Business Office Using Technology
Incorporating Technology Strategies into your Business Plans
Pro's and Cons of Business Communication Technology
Don't have time to worry about the IT set up? Serviced executive office suites come with telecoms, cabling and high speed internet as standard. Find your "ready to work" office space now.
OpenTechSupport.net Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how OpenTechSupport.net uses and protects any information that you give OpenTechSupport.net when you use this website.
OpenTechSupport.net is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
OpenTechSupport.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 18th, March, 2015.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy please contact us using the feedback form.
Home Feedback
Privacy Policy
OpenTechSupport.net
- Business Technology Site and contents are © OpenTechSupport.net - All Rights Reserved 2016 - 2020
